export default data6 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "What is the capital city of Northern Ireland?",
        options: ["Belfast", "Dublin", "Cork", "Edinburgh"],
        correct_option: "Belfast"
    },
    {
        id: "q2",
        question: "When is Halloween celebrated?",
        options: ["5th of November", "11th of November", "31st of October", "1st of April"],
        correct_option: "31st of October"
    },
    {
        id: "q3",
        question: "The Bill of Rights in 1689 gave women the right to vote.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
    {
        id: "q4",
        question: "What is the name of the most famous cricket competition played between England and Australia?",
        options: ["The Ashes", "The Six Nations Championship", "The Grand National", "The Australian Open"],
        correct_option: "The Ashes"
    },
    {
        id: "q5",
        question: "What was the biggest source of employment during the 18th century?",
        options: ["Fishing", "Teaching", "Aircraft industry", "Manufacturing"],
        correct_option: "Manufacturing"
    },
    {
        id: "q6",
        question: "Which Scottish clan was killed for not taking the oath?",
        options: ["The MacLaine of Lochbuie", "The McDowalls of Garthland", "The Macpherson of Cluny", "The MacDonalds of Glencoe"],
        correct_option: "The MacDonalds of Glencoe"
    },
    {
        id: "q7",
        question: "The assassination of the Archduke Franz Ferdinand of Austria in 1914 led to which of the following wars?",
        options: ["The Crimean War", "The First World War", "The Civil War", "The Second World War"],
        correct_option: "The First World War"
    },
    {
        id: "q8",
        question: "What is the capital city of Scotland?",
        options: ["Glasgow", "St Andrews", "Edinburgh", "Aberdeen"],
        correct_option: "Edinburgh"
    },
    {
        id: "q9",
        question: "In 1833 the Emancipation Act abolished slavery throughout the British Empire.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
    {
        id: "q10",
        question: "The Falkland Islands are a British overseas territory and are part of the United Kingdom.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
    {
        id: "q11",
        question: "What was the name of the activist group who fought for the women’s right to vote?",
        options: ["Chartists", "Beefeaters", "Suffragettes", "Quakers"],
        correct_option: "Suffragettes"
    },
    {
        id: "q12",
        question: "What UK landmark was voted as Britain’s favourite view in 2007?",
        options: ["The Big Ben", "Lake District", "Snowdonia", "The London Eye"],
        correct_option: "Lake District"
    },
    {
        id: "q13",
        question: "Who were the first people to live in Britain in what we call the Stone Age?",
        options: ["Farmers", "Peasants", "Hunter-gatherers", "Pirates"],
        correct_option: "Hunter-gatherers"
    },
    {
        id: "q14",
        question: "What do you need to do to apply for a National Insurance Number?",
        options: ["Contact the NHS", "Contact the Department for Work and Pensions (DWP", "Contact your local MP", "Ask you employer to get it for you"],
        correct_option: "Contact the Department for Work and Pensions (DWP"
    },
    {
        id: "q15",
        question: "Which of the following is a major horse-racing event in England?",
        options: ["The Wimbledon Championship", "Royal Ascot", "The Open Championship", "The Six Nations Championship"],
        correct_option: "Royal Ascot"
    },
    {
        id: "q16",
        question: "How many members form a jury in Scotland?",
        options: ["12", "14", "15", "20"],
        correct_option: "15"
    },
    {
        id: "q17",
        question: "What is known as Lent?",
        options: ["The 40 days before Christmas", "The 40 days after Easter", "The 40 days before Easter", "The 40 days after Christmas"],
        correct_option: "The 40 days before Easter"
    },
    {
        id: "q18",
        question: "When was the last successful foreign invasion of England?",
        options: ["1415", "1314", "1066", "1200"],
        correct_option: "1066"
    },
    {
        id: "q19",
        question: "When did people learn to make bronze?",
        options: ["Around 3,000 years ago", "Around 4,000 years ago", "Around 5,000 years ago", "Around 2,000 years ago"],
        correct_option: "Around 4,000 years ago"
    },
    {
        id: "q20",
        question: "When is the Jewish celebration known as Hanukkah normally celebrated?",
        options: ["June or July", "October or November", "November or December", "March or April"],
        correct_option: "November or December"
    },
    {
        id: "q21",
        question: "What musical award is given during the Mercury Music Prize?",
        options: ["Best album from the UK", "Best album from the UK and Ireland", "Best solo artist from the UK", "Best solo artist the UK and Ireland"],
        correct_option: "Best album from the UK and Ireland"
    },
    {
        id: "q22",
        question: "Where is the five-day race meeting attended by members of the Royal Family and known as Royal Ascot celebrated?",
        options: ["In Luton", "In Berkshire", "In Salisbury", "In Kent"],
        correct_option: "In Berkshire"
    },
    {
        id: "q23",
        question: "Who was the first person to lead a Roman invasion in Britain in 55 BC?",
        options: ["Emperor Claudius", "Julius Caesar", "Napoleon", "William Caxton"],
        correct_option: "Julius Caesar"
    },
    {
        id: "q24",
        question: "Which court deals with minor criminal cases in England, Wales and Northern Ireland?",
        options: ["The Justice of the Peace Court", "The Magistrates’ Court", "The High Court", "The Crown Court"],
        correct_option: "The Magistrates’ Court"
    }
    
    
]